(Leonard:)I thought I could try to analyze you
and get to the root of your anxiety.
(Sheldon:)What qualifies you to attempt
to understand my mind?
(Leonard:)My mother is a highly regarded
psychiatrist...
(Leonard:)...and I've been in therapy
ever since...
(Leonard:)...she accused me
of breast feeding co-dependently.
And Raj says he can teach you--
What did you call it?
(Sheldon:)I don't know,
some Indian meditation crap.
I see. I assume since the rest of you
have set the bar so low...
(Sheldon:)...you're saving the most impressive
contribution for last.
(Sheldon:)Go ahead, Howard. Dazzle me.
(Howard:)My power is the ability to pretend
like I give a damn...
(Howard:)...about your piddly-ass problems.
And that's 24/7, buddy.
And I appreciate the pretense.
(Penny:)So, what do you say, Sheldon?
Are we your X-Men?